Sentence #,Word,Tag
Sentence: 1,John,B-per
,",",O
,a,O
,skilled,O
,software,B-occu
,developer,I-occu
,at,O
,Microsoft,B-org
,",",O
,created,O
,a,O
,new,O
,application,O
,to,O
,streamline,O
,business,O
,processes,O
,",",O
,showcasing,O
,his,O
,innovation,O
,and,O
,expertise,O
,in,O
,software,O
,solutions,O
,.,O
Sentence: 2,Sarah,B-per
,",",O
,the,O
,diligent,O
,project,B-occu
,manager,I-occu
,at,O
,Google,B-org
,",",O
,ensured,O
,that,O
,her,O
,team,O
,",",O
,including,O
,John,B-per
,and,O
,Lisa,B-per
,",",O
,the,O
,UI/UX,B-occu
,designer,I-occu
,",",O
,met,O
,the,O
,tight,O
,deadline,O
,for,O
,the,O
,software,O
,release,O
,",",O
,coordinating,O
,efforts,O
,for,O
,a,O
,successful,O
,project,O
,delivery,O
,.,O
Sentence: 3,Michael,B-per
,",",O
,a,O
,meticulous,O
,QA,B-occu
,engineer,I-occu
,with,O
,Apple,B-org
,",",O
,rigorously,O
,tested,O
,every,O
,feature,O
,",",O
,collaborating,O
,with,O
,Sarah,B-per
,and,O
,David,B-per
,",",O
,the,O
,database,B-occu
,administrator,I-occu
,",",O
,to,O
,guarantee,O
,a,O
,bug-free,O
,software,O
,experience,O
,and,O
,maintain,O
,high-quality,O
,standards,O
,.,O
Sentence: 4,Lisa,B-per
,",",O
,a,O
,dedicated,O
,system,B-occu
,analyst,I-occu
,at,O
,IBM,B-org
,",",O
,collaborated,O
,with,O
,John,B-per
,and,O
,Emily,B-per
,",",O
,the,O
,UI/UX,B-occu
,designer,I-occu
,",",O
,to,O
,analyze,O
,the,O
,client's,O
,requirements,O
,and,O
,design,O
,a,O
,customized,O
,software,O
,solution,O
,",",O
,aligning,O
,the,O
,product,O
,with,O
,specific,O
,user,O
,needs,O
,.,O
Sentence: 5,Emily,B-per
,",",O
,the,O
,talented,O
,UI/UX,B-occu
,designer,I-occu
,at,O
,Adobe,B-org
,",",O
,collaborated,O
,with,O
,Lisa,B-per
,and,O
,David,B-per
,",",O
,the,O
,database,B-occu
,administrator,I-occu
,",",O
,crafting,O
,an,O
,intuitive,O
,interface,O
,that,O
,enhanced,O
,the,O
,user,O
,experience,O
,",",O
,prioritizing,O
,aesthetics,O
,and,O
,usability,O
,.,O
Sentence: 6,David,B-per
,",",O
,a,O
,skilled,O
,database,B-occu
,administrator,I-occu
,with,O
,Oracle,B-org
,",",O
,optimized,O
,the,O
,database,O
,performance,O
,for,O
,faster,O
,query,O
,execution,O
,",",O
,collaborating,O
,with,O
,Emily,B-per
,and,O
,Olivia,B-per
,",",O
,the,O
,network,B-occu
,administrator,I-occu
Sentence: 7,Olivia,B-per
,",",O
,the,O
,network,B-occu
,administrator,I-occu
,at,O
,Cisco,B-org
,",",O
,collaborated,O
,with,O
,David,B-per
,and,O
,Michael,B-per
,",",O
,the,O
,QA,B-occu
,engineer,I-occu
,",",O
,resolving,O
,connectivity,O
,issues,O
,to,O
,maintain,O
,a,O
,seamless,O
,workflow,O
,",",O
,ensuring,O
,uninterrupted,O
,software,O
,development,O
,.,O
Sentence: 8,Brian,B-per
,",",O
,a,O
,technical,B-occu
,support,I-occu
,engineer,I-occu
,at,O
,Dell,B-org
,",",O
,collaborated,O
,with,O
,Olivia,B-per
,and,O
,John,B-per
,",",O
,the,O
,software,B-occu
,developer,I-occu
,",",O
,providing,O
,prompt,O
,assistance,O
,to,O
,resolve,O
,software,O
,issues,O
,",",O
,offering,O
,valuable,O
,support,O
,to,O
,end-users,O
,.,O
Sentence: 9,Rachel,B-per
,",",O
,a,O
,business,B-occu
,analyst,I-occu
,at,O
,SAP,B-org
,",",O
,collaborated,O
,with,O
,Lisa,B-per
,and,O
,Mark,B-per
,",",O
,the,O
,Scrum,B-occu
,master,I-occu
,",",O
,conducting,O
,market,O
,research,O
,to,O
,identify,O
,opportunities,O
,for,O
,improvement,O
,",",O
,contributing,O
,to,O
,informed,O
,development,O
,decisions,O
,.,O
Sentence: 10,Alex,B-per
,",",O
,a,O
,proficient,O
,DevOps,B-occu
,engineer,I-occu
,at,O
,Amazon,B-org
,Web,I-org
,Services,I-org
,",",O
,collaborated,O
,with,O
,John,B-per
,and,O
,Brian,B-per
,",",O
,the,O
,technical,B-occu
,support,I-occu
,engineer,I-occu
,",",O
,to,O
,automate,O
,deployment,O
,processes,O
,",",O
,improving,O
,overall,O
,efficiency,O
,and,O
,productivity,O
,.,O
Sentence: 11,Legal,B-occu
,counsel,I-occu
,at,O
,Oracle,B-org
,",",O
,including,O
,Lisa,B-per
,",",O
,reviewed,O
,and,O
,approved,O
,contracts,O
,to,O
,protect,O
,the,O
,software,O
,house's,O
,interests,O
,",",O
,ensuring,O
,legal,O
,compliance,O
,and,O
,safeguarding,O
,intellectual,O
,property,O
,.,O
Sentence: 12,The,O
,finance,B-occu
,and,I-occu
,accounting,I-occu
,analyst,I-occu
,at,O
,"Ernst & Young,",B-org
,including,O
,Emma,B-per
,and,O
,Steven,B-per
,",",O
,managed,O
,the,O
,budget,O
,and,O
,financial,O
,aspects,O
,of,O
,software,O
,"projects,",O
,optimizing,O
,resource,O
,allocation,O
,.,O
Sentence:13,Emma,B-per
,",",O
,a,O
,content,B-occu
,writer,I-occu
,at,O
,"Adobe,",B-org
,created,O
,informative,O
,blog,O
,posts,O
,to,O
,showcase,O
,the,O
,software's,O
,"features,",O
,effectively,O
,communicating,O
,the,O
,product's,O
,value,O
,to,O
,the,O
,target,O
,audience,O
,.,O
Sentence:15,Software,B-occu
,developers,I-occu
,at,O
,Google,B-org
,often,O
,collaborate,O
,on,O
,complex,O
,coding,O
,projects,O
,to,O
,create,O
,innovative,O
,"solutions,",O
,with,O
,teams,O
,contributing,O
,to,O
,groundbreaking,O
,advancements,O
,in,O
,technology,O
,.,O
Sentence: 16,The,O
,project,B-occu
,"manager,",O
,"Steven,",B-per
,at,O
,Amazon,B-org
,Web,I-org
,"Services,",I-org
,coordinated,O
,tasks,O
,and,O
,ensured,O
,the,O
,timely,O
,completion,O
,of,O
,software,B-occu
,"milestones,",O
,overseeing,O
,project,B-occu
,delivery,O
,with,O
,efficiency,O
,.,O
Sentence: 17,"Angela,",B-per
,a,O
,QA,B-occu
,engineer,I-occu
,at,O
,Apple,B-org
,",",O
,rigorously,O
,tested,O
,software,O
,applications,O
,to,O
,identify,O
,and,O
,fix,O
,any,O
,"defects,",O
,maintaining,O
,high-quality,O
,standards,O
,in,O
,the,O
,final,O
,product,O
,.,O
Sentence:18,the,O
,system,B-occu
,analyst,I-occu
,at,O
,IBM,B-org
,",",O
,played,O
,a,O
,key,O
,role,O
,in,O
,designing,O
,scalable,O
,and,O
,efficient,O
,software,O
,systems,O
,",",O
,contributing,O
,to,O
,the,O
,development,O
,of,O
,robust,O
,and,O
,adaptable,O
,solutions,O
,.,O
Senetence:19,Emily,B-per
,",",O
,the,O
,UI/UX,B-occu
,designer,I-occu
,at,O
,Adobe,B-org
,",",O
,focused,O
,on,O
,creating,O
,visually,O
,appealing,O
,and,O
,user-friendly,O
,software,O
,interfaces,O
,",",O
,prioritizing,O
,aesthetics,O
,and,O
,usability,O
,.,O
Sentence: 20,a,O
,database,B-occu
,administrator,I-occu
,with,O
,Oracle,B-org
,",",O
,maintained,O
,the,O
,integrity,O
,and,O
,security,O
,of,O
,the,O
,software,O
,database,O
,",",O
,implementing,O
,measures,O
,to,O
,safeguard,O
,sensitive,O
,information,O
,.,O
Sentence:21,Emily,B-per
,",",O
,a,O
,QA,B-occu
,engineer,I-occu
,at,O
,Microsoft,B-org
,",",O
,conducted,O
,thorough,O
,testing,O
,to,O
,identify,O
,and,O
,fix,O
,bugs,O
,",",O
,ensuring,O
,a,O
,flawless,O
,user,O
,experience,O
,for,O
,their,O
,latest,O
,software,O
,release,O
,.,O
Sentence:22,David,B-per
,",",O
,the,O
,system,B-occu
,analyst,I-occu
,at,O
,IBM,B-org
,",",O
,analyzed,O
,user,O
,requirements,O
,to,O
,design,O
,a,O
,user-friendly,O
,software,O
,system,O
,",",O
,focusing,O
,on,O
,creating,O
,solutions,O
,that,O
,catered,O
,to,O
,specific,O
,user,O
,needs,O
,.,O
Sentence: 23,Jessica,B-per
,",",O
,the,O
,UI/UX,B-occu
,designer,I-occu
,at,O
,Apple,B-org
,",",O
,concentrated,O
,on,O
,creating,O
,visually,O
,appealing,O
,and,O
,intuitive,O
,software,O
,interfaces,O
,",",O
,enhancing,O
,the,O
,overall,O
,user,O
,experience,O
,and,O
,product,O
,aesthetics,O
,.,O
Sentence: 24,Brian,B-per
,",",O
,a,O
,database,B-occu
,administrator,I-occu
,with,O
,Google,B-org
,",",O
,optimized,O
,database,B-occu
,queries,O
,for,O
,improved,O
,software,O
,performance,O
,",",O
,contributing,O
,to,O
,the,O
,efficiency,O
,of,O
,data,O
,retrieval,O
,and,O
,storage,O
,.,O
Sentence: 25,Olivia,B-per
,",",O
,the,O
,network,B-occu
,administrator,I-occu
,at,O
,Cisco,B-org
,",",O
,resolved,O
,network,O
,issues,O
,to,O
,ensure,O
,uninterrupted,O
,software,O
,development,O
,",",O
,maintaining,O
,a,O
,smooth,O
,workflow,O
,for,O
,collaborative,O
,work,O
,.,O
Sentence: 26,Rachel,B-per
,",",O
,a,O
,technical,B-occu
,support,I-occu
,engineer,I-occu
,at,O
,Dell,B-org
,",",O
,provided,O
,timely,O
,assistance,O
,to,O
,software,B-occu
,users,O
,facing,O
,issues,O
,",",O
,offering,O
,valuable,O
,support,O
,and,O
,solutions,O
,to,O
,end-users,O
,.,O
Sentence: 27,Mark,B-per
,",",O
,a,O
,business,B-occu
,analyst,I-occu
,at,O
,Amazon,B-org
,",",O
,gathered,O
,and,O
,analyzed,O
,data,O
,to,O
,make,O
,informed,O
,software,B-occu
,development,O
,decisions,O
,",",O
,contributing,O
,to,O
,strategic,O
,planning,O
,and,O
,product,B-occu
,improvements,O
,.,O
Sentence: 28,Alex,B-per
,",",O
,the,O
,DevOps,B-occu
,engineer,I-occu
,at,O
,Salesforce,B-org
,",",O
,automated,O
,software,O
,deployment,O
,processes,O
,to,O
,enhance,O
,efficiency,O
,",",O
,streamlining,O
,workflows,O
,for,O
,faster,O
,and,O
,more,O
,reliable,O
,releases,O
,.,O
Sentence: 29,The,
,marketing,O
,team,O
,at,O
,Adobe,B-org
,",",O
,including,O
,Angela,B-per
,and,O
,Emma,B-per
,",",O
,effectively,O
,promoted,O
,the,O
,latest,O
,software,O
,release,O
,through,O
,various,O
,channels,O
,",",O
,maximizing,O
,visibility,O
,and,O
,user,O
,engagement,O
,.,O
,The,O
Sentence: 30,front-end,B-occu
,developer,I-occu
,focused,O
,on,O
,crafting,O
,a,O
,visually,O
,appealing,O
,user,O
,interface,O
,that,O
,enhances,O
,user,O
,experience,O
,.,O
Sentence: 31,The,O
,back-end,B-occu
,developer,I-occu
,worked,O
,diligently,O
,to,O
,optimize,O
,server-side,O
,functionalities,O
,for,O
,efficient,O
,data,O
,processing,O
,and,O
,secure,O
,transactions,O
,.,O
